Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode. Subtitles will likely not function properly. Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv: https://mpv.io
Kızıl Bacak Zeff.
You're alive.
Yaşıyordun demek.
No pirate could compare to you, being both a cook and a captain...
Hem aşçılık hem de kaptanlık yapmış, rakipsiz bir korsan.
I'm alive. So what?
Yaşıyorsam ne olmuş?
It's none of your concern.
Bu seni ilgilendirmiyor.
As you can see, I'm passing my time as a cook now.
Gördüğün gibi, artık bir aşçı olarak yaşıyorum.
It sounds better when you say it like that...
Bunu böyle söylemen kulağa hoş geliyor...
but you're not just passing time as a cook.
ama sen sadece zaman geçirmek için aşçılık yapmıyorsun,...
it looks like you can only pass your time as a cook.
sanki yapabildiğin tek şey bu.
Red Leg Zeff was a master of kicks who never used his hands in battle.
Kızıl Bacak Zeff, ellerini kullanmadan dövüşen bir tekme ustasıdır.
His mighty legs were said to shatter bedrock and even leave footprints in steel.
Güçlü bacaklarının kayaları parçalayıp çeliğin üstünde iz bıraktığı söylenir.
And "Red Leg" referred to your boots,
“Kızıl Bacak” lakabı,
washed in the blood of those you kicked into submission.
tekmelediklerinin kanıyla kaplı, alevi andıran çizmelerinden gelir.
But you seem to have lost one of your precious legs...
Ama görüyorum ki, o değerli bacaklarından birini kaybetmişsin.
I guess the rumors were true.
Demek ki söylentiler doğruymuş.
A stroke of bad luck doomed you to an accident at sea.
Denizde böyle bir kaza yaşaman baya şanssızlık.
I suppose losing a leg would mean you've lost the ability to fight.
Bir bacağını kaybetmek dövüş yeteneğini de götürür sanırım.
I don't give a damn about fighting.
Dövüşmek umurumda değil.
I may have lost a leg, but I can cook so long as I have these two hands.
Bir bacağımı kaybettim ama ellerim olduğu sürece yemek yapabilirim.
Whatever it is, get to the damn point already!
Ne demek istiyorsan söyle artık.
Red Leg Zeff,
Kızıl Bacak Zeff,
you once sailed the Grand Line and returned unscathed.
bir keresinde Grand Line'a gittin ve hiç yaralanmadan geri döndün.
You must have the logbook from that year-long voyage.
O bir yıllık yolcuğuluktan kalma bir seyir defterin olması lazım.
Hand it over!
Onu bana ver!
Wow, Boss Man! You sailed the Grand Line, too?!
Vay, ihtiyar! Sen de mi Grand Line'a gittin?!
I did...
Evet...
My logbook, huh?
Seyir defterim, ha?
Sure, I've got what you're looking for.
Evet, istediğin şeye sahibim.
But there's no way in hell I'm giving it to you.
Ama onu sana vermemin imkanı yok.
That logbook is the pride of all those who sailed with me.
O seyir defteri, benimle yolculuk eden herkesin onurunu taşıyor.
The likes of you couldn't even handle it.
Senin gibilere fazla ağır gelir.
Then I'll just have to take it!
O zaman zorla almam gerekecek!
I admit the Grand Line got the better of me.
Grand Line'ın beni yendiğini kabul ediyorum.
That being said, I'm still the indomitable Don Krieg...
Ama yenilgide bile, ben yılmaz Don Krieg
and I had the power necessary to cross such a treacherous sea.
en tehlikeli denizleri geçebilecek güce sahiptim.
I had the men.
Adamlarım vardı.
I had the ambition.
Hırsım vardı.
The only thing I lacked was information.
Tek eksik olan şey bilgiydi.
I just didn't know what to expect.
Sadece neyle karşılaşacağımı bilmiyordum.
I will have that logbook.
O seyir defteri benim olacak.
With it, I will reassemble my pirate fleet, seize the One Piece,
Onunla korsan filomu yeniden toplayıp One Piece’i ele geçireceğim.
and rise to the top of this Great Pirate Era!
Ve bu Büyük Korsan Çağı'nın en tepesine çıkacağım!
Wait just a minute.
Dur bakalım.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Korsanlar Kralı olacak kişi benim!
Cabin Boy?!
Kamarot?!
Hey, back down, Cabin Boy!
Hey, geri dur, Kamarot!
You're no match for him!
Sen onun dengi değilsin!
I can't back down. Not about this.
Geri duramam. Bu konu da olmaz.
Did you say something, kid?
Bir şey mi söyledin, velet?
We can pretend I didn't hear you say that.
Demin söylediklerini görmezden geleceğim.
No need to pretend.
Buna gerek yok.
I'm only stating the facts.
Sadece gerçeği söylüyorum.
This is no game, boy.
Bu bir oyun değil, çocuk.
Of course not.
Haklısın.
I will conquer the Grand Line.
Grand Line'a ben hükmedeceğim.
It's no joke, you brat!
Bu iş şaka değil, velet!
Putting aside what we didn't know,
Bilgi eksikliğimizi bir kenara koyarsak,
our fleet of 5,000 sailors only lasted seven days on that devilish sea!
5,000 kişilik 50 gemim o acımasız denizde sadece yedi gün dayandı!
A kid like you doesn't stand a chance!
Senin gibi bir veledin hiç şansı yok!
S-Seven days?!
Y-Yedi gün mü?
The Krieg Pirates only lasted seven days?!
Krieg Korsanları sadece yedi gün mü dayanabildi?!
What the hell happened to them?!
Onlara ne oldu böyle?!
I'm sorry, but I hate it when people joke around like this.
Üzgünüm ama bu şekilde şaka yapılmasından nefret ediyorum.
If you persist, I'll just crush you right here and now.
Israrına devam edersen, seni burada ezip geçerim.
If you can.
Ezebilirsen tabii.
Perfect.
Nasıl istersen.
As you wish, I'll be sending you to the afterlife.
İstediğin gibi, seni öbür dünyaya yollayacağım.
Gonna fight, Luffy? Need a hand?
Dövüşecek misin, Luffy? Yardım lazım mı?
A-And if you don't need help, th-that's fine too...
Ş-şey, yardıma gerek yoksa da olur tabii...
Zoro! Usopp! I didn't see you there!
Zoro! Usopp! Burada olduğunuzu bilmiyordum!
I'm fine. Just watch from there.
İyiyim ben. Oradan izleyin sadece.
I-If you insist!
T-Tamam.
Are those your men?
Onlar senin adamların mı?
Don't you think your crew is a bit small?!
Bayağı küçük bir tayfan varmış!
What're you talking about?! We have two more!
Ne diyorsun sen?! İki kişi daha var!
Hey! You counted me, didn't you?!
Hey! Beni de saydın, değil mi?!
I'll deal with you later.
Sizinle daha sonra ilgileneceğim.
I'm going to feed my men first.
Önce gidip adamlarımı beslemeliyim.
Anyone who wants to live should clear out before I get back.
Canını seven, ben geri dönmeden buradan ayrılsa iyi olur.
I'm only after your logbook and this ship.
Tek istediğim o seyir defteri ve bu gemi.
If you still want to throw your life away,
Eğer hâlâ hayatınızı önemsemiyorsanız,
I'll spare some time to bury you at sea!
sizi denizin dibine gömeceğim!
Make your choice.
Seçiminizi yapın.
I'm so sorry, Sanji.
Çok üzgünüm, Sanji-san.
I had no idea he'd go this far.
Bu kadar ileri gideceğini bilmiyordum.
You don't need to apologize, grunt.
Özre gerek yok, çaylak.
Every cook here did what they thought was right.
Buradaki her aşçı neyin doğru olduğunu düşündülerse onu yaptılar.
That's all there is to it.
Hepsi bu.
Chef Zeff!
Patron!
You're not seriously taking Sanji's side in this, are you?
Ciddi ciddi Sanji'nin tarafını tutmuyorsun, değil mi?
That's right!
Evet!
It's his fault this happened!
Olanların hepsi onun suçu!
He's trying to destroy your precious restaurant!
Sizin değerli restoranınızı yok etmeye çalışıyor!
Shut up, you damn eggplants!
Susun artık, sizi lanet patlıcanlar!
Have you ever felt such hunger you thought you'd die?!
Hiç açlıktan öleceğinizi düşündüğünüz bir an oldu mu?!
Can you comprehend the terror of running out of food and water on this vast ocean?!
Bu sonsuz denizde aç ve susuz kalmanın ne denli...
Can you comprehend such suffering?!
acı ve dehşet verici olduğunu anlayabilir misiniz?!
Huh?
Ha?
Ch-Chef Zeff, what do you mean?
N-Ne demek istiyorsunuz, Patron?!
If all you're going to do is bitch and moan,
Sanji’nin sizden farkı, ne demek istediğimi anlamasıdır.
I'll stay and fight.
Ben burada kalıp dövüşeceğim!
I'm too pissed off to let myself get whupped like that!
Öylece kaçıp gitmek için fazla sinirliyim!
I'm staying too! This is where I work after all!
Ben de! Burası benim çalıştığım yer!
We have nowhere else to go anyway!
Gidecek başka yerimiz yok zaten!
What are you doing?!
Ne yapıyorsunuz?!
You saw what the don is capable of!
Don'un neler yapabileceğini gördünüz!
Hey, Gin!
Hey, Gin!
Let me tell you something.
Sana bir şey söyleyeyim.
My duty as a cook is to feed those who are hungry.
Bir aşçı olarak benim görevim, karnı aç olanları beslemektir.
That said...
Ama...
when those looters turn on me with full bellies...
o yağmacılar, tok karınlarıyla yedikleri kaba sıçarlarsa
I don't want to hear you complain when I beat up your fellow pirates.
korsan arkadaşlarını pataklarken sesini çıkarmayasın!
Just try to take this restaurant,
Eğer bu restorana el uzatırsanız...
and I'll kill you without a second thought.
bir an bile düşünmeden sizi öldürüm.
Understood?
Anladın mı?
You'd kill him after saving his life? You're hopeless, Sanji...
Önce kurtarıp sonra öldürmek mi? Umutsuz vakanın tekisin, Sanji.
Shut up, you crappy cook!
Kapa çeneni, berbat aşçı!
See? He's pretty cool, huh?!
Şuna bakın! Çok havalı değil mi?!
That's nice, but enough about him!
O kimin umurunda?!
We have to get out of here!
Buradan gitmemiz lazım!
Settle down!
Sakin ol!
He may be Krieg, but he's in bad shape.
Krieg olsa bile, şu anda bitik durumda.
Gin, you said you don't know anything about the Grand Line, didn't you?
Gin, Grand Line hakkında hiçbir şey bilmediğini söylemiştin ama,
But you've been there.
oraya gittin, değil mi?!
I still don't know a thing about the Grand Line.
Orası hakkında hiçbir şey bilmediğim doğru.
What we saw on our seventh day on the Grand Line...
Grand Line'daki yedinci günümüzde gördüğümüz şey...
I don't know if it was a dream...
bir hayal de olabilir,
or reality...
gerçek de...
I still can't wrap my head around it.
Hala daha kafamı toparlayamıyorum.
It was unbelievable!
İnanılmaz bir şeydi!
How could a lone man...
Yalnız bir adam, nasıl...
destroy a fleet of fifty ships?!
50 gemiden oluşan bir filoyu yok edebilir?!
– What?!
– Ne?!
It happened out of nowhere.
Bir anda oluverdi.
Before we even realized he was there,
Biz daha onun orada olduğunu anlayamadan,
the ships began to sink, one after another.
gemiler ardı ardına batmaya başladı.
If we hadn't been lucky enough to encounter that storm,
O fırtına ile karşılaşmamış olsaydık,
our flagship would have met the same fate.
ana gemimiz de aynı kader ile yüzleşecekti.
I don't know how many of our ships survived.
Kaç tane gemimizin hayatta kaldığını bilmiyorum.
It's just too horrible to believe it was real.
Gerçek olduğunu kabul etmek için fazla korkunçtu.
I want to forget what happened!
Hatırlamak istemiyorum!
I want to forget that man—
O adamı unutmak istiyorum—
how he could seemingly kill with just a glance—
sadece bir bakışıyla nasıl öldürebildiğini—
with that hawk-like glare!
o şahin gibi bakışıyla!
What?!
Ne?!
Huh?
Ha?
Could it be...?!
Yoksa...?!
There's no mistaking it.
O muhtemelen...
That must be the man known as Hawk Eye.
Şahin Göz olarak bilinen adam.
What?
Ne?
Just telling us that his eyes were like those of a hawk wouldn't be proof alone.
Sadece gözlerinin şahin gibi olması, kanıt sayılmaz.
But knowing he was capable of something so devastating is plenty convincing for me.
Böyle bir yıkımı yaratabilecek olması, o olduğunu işaret eden güçlü bir delil.
The hawk-eyed man!
Şahin gözlü adam!
Huh? Do you know him, Zoro?
Ha? Tanıyor musun, Zoro?
Yeah...
Evet...
It's who I've been looking for.
O benim aradığım kişi.
Is it possible he had some sort of grudge against your crew?
O adam sizin tayfanıza karşı bir kin besliyor olmalı.
I'd never seen him before!
Onu daha önce hiç görmedim!
Maybe you woke him from a nap or something.
Onu uykusundan falan uyandırmışsınızdır belki de.
Don't be ridiculous!
Saçmalamayın!
Who the hell smashes an entire fleet over that?!
Kim böyle bir şey için bir filoyu yok eder?!
Don't get so worked up.
Bu kadar sinirlenme.
It's just an example.
Ben sadece...
That is, it's an example of what kind of place the Grand Line is.
Grand Line'da böyle şeylerin mümkün olduğunu söylüyorum.
What kind of place is that?!
Ne tür bir yer orası?!
A place where anything could happen.
Her şeyin olabileceği bir yer.
Hey Luffy, we shouldn't go somewhere like that!
Hey Luffy, öyle bir yere gitmemeliyiz!
Luffy!
Luffy!
Hey, Luffy?
Hey, Luffy?
Whoa, that's so freaking cool!
Vay, çok heyecanlandım!
I knew it had to be crazy there!
Öyle bir yer olduğunu biliyordum!
At least acknowledge how dangerous it is!
En azından ne kadar tehlikeli olduğunu kabullen!
Well, that settles it. My only goal at this point is the Grand Line.
Bununla beraber, artık tek hedefim kesinlikle Grand Line.
What?!
Ne?!
I'll find him there...
O adamı...
I'll find that man on the Grand Line!
O adamı Grand Line'da bulacağım!
Are you nuts?
Delirdin mi sen?
You're the type to charge in and die first.
Tam olarak, önden saldırıp ölecek bir tipsin.
You're right, but saying I'm "nuts" is going too far.
Haklısın aslında, ama bana deli demekle ileri gidiyorsun.
I threw my life away when I decided to be the world's greatest swordsman.
Dünyanın en iyi kılıç ustası olmayı seçtiğimde zaten hayatımı çöpe attım.
Only one person can call me nuts, and that person is me!
Sadece tek bir kişi bana deli diyebilir ve o kişi de benim!
Yeah, the same goes for me!
Evet, benim için de aynısı geçerli!
Yeah, me too, since I'm a man of the sea and all!
Aynı şekilde ben de, sonuçta denizciyim!
In your case, that's a lie.
Yalan söylüyorsun.
Ridiculous...
Saçmalık...
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey!
Do you numbskulls have any idea what's going on here?!
Siz mankafalar burada neler döndüğünün farkında mısınız?!
Outside this restaurant is a massive galleon from Pirate Commodore Don Krieg's fleet!
Dışarıda, Komodor Don Krieg’in filosuna ait devasa bir kalyon var!
You can build your castles in the sky when the battle is over!
Bu savaş bittiğinde istediğiniz hayali kurabilirsiniz!
– We're saved!
– Kurtulduk!
This is great! We're gonna live!
Bu harika! Yaşayacağız!
It's like I'm dreaming!
Sanki bir rüya gibi!
We're free from that nightmare!
Bu kabustan kurtulduk!
We made it back alive from the Pirate Graveyard!
Korsan Mezarlığı'ndan canlı çıktık!
That's right...
Bu doğru...
We can once again turn our sights on the Grand Line.
Gözlerimizi bir kez daha Grand Line'a dikebiliriz.
Huh?
Ha?
What's with those looks?
Bu bakışlar da ne?
W-We're going back there?!
O-Oraya geri mi döneceğiz?!
Any other objections?
Başka itirazı olan var mı?
First,
İlk olarak,
we'll abandon this irreparable wreck and take over the restaurant.
bu tamir edilemez gemiyi terk edip o restoranı ele geçireceğiz.
Our enemy is a staff of punk cooks.
Çalışanları bir grup haydutumsu aşçıdan ibaret.
They've got nothing on us.
Bize karşı hiç şansları yok.
Attack!
Saldırın!
They're coming! I can hear them yelling!
Geliyorlar! Bağırışlarını duyabiliyorum!
Hold them off! This ship— this restaurant is ours!
Onları uzak tutun! Bu gemi bizim restoranımız!
Make way, you scum!
Yolu açın, sizi pislikler!
What was that?!
O da neydi?!
What happened?!
Ne oldu?!
Don Krieg!
Don Krieg!
Our flagship was...
Ana gemimiz...
sliced in half!
ikiye bölündü!
Sliced in half?! Did I hear that right?!
İkiye mi bölündü?! Doğru mu duydum?!
Our massive galleon?!
Bizim devasa kalyon mu?!
How could...
Böylesi...
something so preposterous happen?!
imkansız bir şey nasıl olabilir?!
Weigh anchor!
Demir atın!
It'll bring the whole ship down!
Bütün gemiyi yok edecek!
Yes, sir!
Emredersiniz!
Not good!
Hiç iyi değil!
Nami, Yosaku, and Johnny are on the ship out front!
Nami, Yosaku ve Johnny ön taraftaki gemide!
Dammit! It's probably too late!
Kahretsin! Muhtemelen çoktan geç kaldık!
Big Bro!
Abi!
Yosaku! Johnny!
Yosaku! Johnny!
Are you guys okay?
İyi misiniz?
Where's the ship?! It's gone! What happened to Nami?!
Gemi nerede?! Gitmiş! Nami'ye ne oldu?!
Well...
Şey...
I'm sorry, Big Bro! She's already gone!
Üzgünüm, abi! O çoktan gitti!
See ya! Tell Luffy and his crew...
Görüşürüz! Luffy ve diğerlerine şöyle söyleyin...
Big Sis Nami...!
Nami Abla...!
"If fate allows, let's meet again!"
"Kaderde varsa, yine karşılaşırız."
She took all the treasure and ran off!
Tüm hazineyi aldı ve kaçtı!
– Wha...?!
– N...?!
– What did you say?!
– Ne dedin?!
That man...
O adam...
What'd you say?!
Ne diyorsunuz siz?!
Nami ran off with the Going Merry?!
Nami Going Merry'yi alıp kaçtı mı?!
What the hell is she doing?!
Ne yaptığını sanıyor ki?!
It happened just a moment ago!
Daha az önce oldu!
What's the matter, Big Sis Nami?
Bir sorun mu var, Nami Abla?
Huh?
Ha?
What's with the wanted posters?
Bu posterlere bakıyorsun da.
Ah... It's nothing.
Ah... Hiçbir şey...
You just continue to impress.
Her zamanki gibi etkileyicisin.
I see a big bounty has caught your eye.
Görüyorum ki büyük bir ödül dikkatini çekmiş.
But I'll tell you that Arlong's the one pirate to steer clear of.
Ama Arlong, peşinden gitmemen gereken bir korsan.
They say he's freakishly strong.
Acayip güçlü olduğunu söylüyorlar.
He had been laying low for a while...
Uzun süre sessiz sedasız takılıyordu, şimdi tekrar fırtına koparıyor.
Though it's hard to resist that 20-million-berry bounty,
Ama o 20 milyon beli'lik ödülden vazgeçmek de zor tabii.
this guy's so strong that even we might be a hair's width from death if we fought.
Bu adam o kadar güçlü ki, savaşsak ölümle burun buruna geliriz.
– Huh?
– Ha?
Big Sis Nami?
Nami Abla?
So sorry, but can you turn around? I need to get changed.
Affedersiniz, üzerimi değiştireceğim, arkanızı döner misiniz?
– What?!
– Ne?!
W-Well...
Ş-Şey...
Change? Here? Now?!
Değiştirmek? Burada? Şimdi?!
If you don't mind.
Sakıncası yoksa.
– Please go ahead!
– Devam edin, lütfen!
She's as bold as she looks!
Gerçekten de göründüğü kadar cesur!
It wouldn't hurt if we took a quick peek, would it?
Bir göz atmaktan zarar gelmez, değil mi?
Not one bit!
Hiç olmaz!
Wh-What are you doing?!
N-Ne yapıyorsun?!
What am I doing? Just a little business.
Ne mi yapıyorum? İş, tabii ki!
I'm a thief who steals from pirates.
Ben korsanlardan çalan bir hırsızım.
I'll be taking the ship now.
Bu gemiyi alıyorum.
I never said that I was a member of their crew.
Tayfadan biri olduğumu asla söylemedim.
It was just an alliance.
Sadece bir ittifaktı.
I only spent a short time with Luffy and his pals, but I had a lot of fun.
Luffy ve diğerleriyle kısa bir zaman geçirdim ama çok eğlendim.
Tell them this:
Onlara şöyle söyleyin:
"If fate allows, let's meet again."
"Kaderde varsa, yine karşılaşırız."
Big Sis Nami!
Nami Abla!
W-Wait! You can't do that!
D-Dur! Bunu yapamazsın!
We were supposed to keep watch of the ship!
Bizden gemiye göz kulak olmamız söylenmişti!
And that's how the ship got taken away...
Ve işte gemiyi böyle aldı...
We're sorry!
Üzgünüz!
Dammit!
Kahretsin!
Just when things couldn't get any worse...!
Bizim için bu krizi daha da kötü hale getirdi!
Kaya gave us that ship!
Bize o gemiyi Kaya vermişti!
Wait! I can still see it!
Bekle! Onu hala görebiliyorum!
It's the Going Merry!
Bu Going Merry!
Where's your ship?
Sizin geminiz nerede?
We still have it here...
Hala burada duruyor...
Zoro! Usopp! Get going!
Zoro! Usopp! Hemen gidin!
Take their ship and follow Nami!
O gemiye binin ve Nami'yi takip edin!
Forget about it. Just let her have the ship.
Unut gitsin. Bırak gemiyi alsın.
We're better off not going after that woman.
O kadının arkasından gitmeye gerek yok.
I won't accept anyone but her as our navigator!
Başka kimseyi rotacımız istemiyorum!
Fine, have it your way... What a high-maintenance captain.
Tamam, nasıl istiyorsan... Ne zahmetli kaptansın ama!
Hey, Usopp! Let's go!
Hey, Usopp! Gidelim!
O-Okay...
T-Tamam...
– Big Bro Zoro, the ship is ready!
– Zoro abi, gemi hazır!
Luffy, what about you?
Luffy, peki sen?
I can't go until I settle things here at the restaurant.
Bu restorandaki işim henüz bitmediği için ayrılamam.
Be careful.
Dikkatli ol.
There's something fishy going on here.
Buradaki durum hiç normal değil.
Yeah, I can tell.
Evet, biliyorum.
The ship's been split in half!
Gemi ikiye bölündü!
Look! Over there!
Şuna bak!
I-I-It's him!
B-B-Bu o!
Don Krieg! It's that man!
Don Krieg! Bu o!
It's the man who destroyed our fleet!
Bu filomuzu yok eden adam!
Th-That man...
O-O adam...
He's the one that...
Yani o adam...
That damn mangy cur!
Şu lanet uyuz köpek!
He chased us all the way here...
Bizi öldürmek için...
to kill us!
buraya kadar takip etmiş!
We're screwed!
Hapı yuttuk!
Zoro?
Zoro?
Who's that?
O da kim?
The man I've been looking for.
Aradığım kişi.
Hawk Eye Mihawk!
Şahin Göz Mihawk!
Hawk Eye Mihawk...
Şahin Göz Mihawk...
The world's greatest...
Dünyadaki en güçlü adam...
So he's the one who single-handedly sank Krieg's fifty ships in the Grand Line?
Grand Line'da Krieg'in elli gemisini kendi başına batıran adam o mu?
Then, he must be the one who just obliterated Krieg's ship.
O zaman Krieg'in gemisini yok eden de o olmalı.
He looks just like an ordinary person, though!
Ama sıradan biri gibi görünüyor!
He doesn't seem to have any special weapons either.
Hiçbir özel silahı da yok gibi gözüküyor.
His weapon is on his back...
Silahı sırtında duruyor...
You're kidding!
Şaka yapıyorsun!
Did he really carve up that massive ship using just his sword?!
Cidden o kocaman gemiyi sırtındaki o kılıçla mı doğradı?
He's the master swordsman Hawk Eye,
O kılıç ustalarının efendisi Şahin Göz,
the man who stands at the top of the world of swordsmen.
kılıç ustalarının en tepesinde yer alan adam.
Y-You son of a bitch...
S-Seni orospu çocuğu...
What kind of grudge would make you chase us this far?
Nasıl bir nefret ki bu, hâlâ peşimizdesin?
Just killing time.
Zaman öldürüyorum.
Wha...?! Don't mock us!
Ne...?! Bizimle dalga geçme!
Wh-What?!
N-Ne?!
I'm sure I aimed straight for him!
Direkt ona nişan aldığıma eminim!
He diverted the bullets.
Sektirdi.
He gently changed their course with just the tip of his sword.
Kılıcının ucuyla yönlerini sakince değiştirdi.
That's ridiculous!
Bu saçmalık!
H-Hey! Who are you?!
H-Hey! Sen de kimsin?!
I've never seen someone wield their sword so delicately.
Daha önce kılıcını bu kadar hassas kullanan birini görmemiştim.
Swordplay that relies on force is void of power.
Kuvvete dayalı bir kılıç darbesi güç barındırmaz.
Did you use that sword to slice up this ship as well?
Bu gemiyi de o kılıçla mı doğradın?
Correct.
Doğru.
I see why...
Anlıyorum...
you're the greatest...
Sen en iyisin...
Three swords... Could he be...?!
Üç katana var... Yoksa o...?!
I set out to sea in order to meet you.
Seninle tanışmak için denize açıldım.
What's your goal?
Amacın ne?
To become the greatest!
En iyisi olmak!
How foolish...
Ne kadar aptalca...
They were nice guys...
İyi insanlardı...
I wonder if they'll let me rejoin them if we ever meet again.
Bir daha karşılaşırsak, onlara katılmama izin verirler mi ki?
Will we ever meet again?
Yine karşılaşacak mıyız acaba?
I want to be free...
Özgür olmak istiyorum...
Bell-mère...
Bell-mère-san...
You have time to kill, right? Let's fight!
Zamanın var, değil mi? Hadi dövüşelim!
Th-This guy is... Zoro!
B-Bu adam... Zoro!
Roronoa Zoro of the three-sword style!
Üç-kılıç stili kullanan Roronoa Zoro!
What?!
Ne?!
The Pirate Hunter, huh?
Korsan Avcısı, ha?
That's who he is?!
O mu?!
Hey, we've got a problem, Luffy!
Hey, bu hiç iyi değil, Luffy!
The Going Merry will be out of sight soon!
Going Merry yakında görüşümüzden çıkacak!
Hey, Luffy!
Hey, Luffy!
Fight?
Dövüş mü?
I pity you, child.
Sana acıyorum, zayıf olan.
If you are a competent swordsman,
Eğer yetkin bir kılıç ustasıysan,
you must see the disparity in our abilities without the need to cross swords.
Kılıçlarımızı çekmeden yetenek farkını görebilmen gerekir.
What compels you to bare your fangs at me?
Kılıcını bana doğrultmanın sebebi ne?
Is it courage, or is it ignorance?
Cesaretin mi, yoksa cehaletin mi?
It's my ambition!
Hırsım!
And a promise I made to a dear friend.
Ve değerli bir arkadaşıma verdiğim söz.
H-Hawk Eye Mihawk, the world's greatest swordsman,
D-Dünyanın en iyi kılıç ustası, Şahin Göz Mihawk...
and Pirate Hunter Zoro...
ve Korsan Avcısı Zoro...
What kind of fight will it be?
Ne tür bir dövüş olacak acaba?
There's no one out there who can defeat Big Bro!
Abiyi yenebilecek birinin olmasının imkanı yok!
Y-Yeah!
E-Evet!
Big Bro is already the strongest!
Abi zaten en güçlü olan!
Hey, what are you planning to do with that?
Hey, bu da ne demek oluyor?
I'm not some brute who hunts rabbits with a cannon.
Tavşan avlamak için top kullanan bir ahmak değilim.
Even if you're a swordsman of some renown,
Ünlü bir kılıç ustası olsan bile,
this sea, the East Blue, is the weakest among the four seas.
bu deniz, Doğu Mavi, dört deniz arasından en güçsüzüdür.
Unfortunately, this is the smallest blade on my person.
Ne yazık ki, yanımda bundan daha küçük bir kılıç yok.
Stop underestimating me!
Bu kadar dalga geçtiğin yeter!
Better not regret it when I kill you!
Seni öldürdüğümde pişman olmazsan iyi olur!
Frog in the well...
Kuyudaki kurbağa...
learn just how big this world is.
dünyanın büyüklüğünü kavra.
Oni Giri!
Şeytan Kesişi!
Wh-What?!
N-Ne?!
Zoro?!
Zoro?!
How...? Big Bro's Oni Giri was stopped!
Ne...? Abi'nin "Şeytan Kesişi"ni durdurdu!
His big finisher never fails to blow away his enemies, but it...!
O teknik düşmanları her seferinde savurur, fakat...!
What's going on?!
Neler oluyor?!
I... I can't move them! What did he do?!
O... Onları hareket ettiremiyorum! Ne yaptı o öyle?!
This move lands every time, but he stopped it using this toy?!
Bu teknikten kurtulan olmamıştı, ama o bir oyuncakla engelledi mi?!
This... can't be happening!
Bu... olamaz!
This is the difference in our abilities?!
Yeteneklerimiz arasında bu kadar mı fark var?!
That can't be right! There's no way it's that far...!
Böyle bir şey olamaz! Bu kadar mesafe olması imkansız.
I can't be this far behind the world!
Dünyanın en güçlüsü bu kadar önde olamaz!
This can't be happening, right, Big Bro?! Get serious!
Bu doğru olamaz, değil mi, abi?! Ciddileş artık!
Big Bro!
Abi!
This distance between us can't be real!
Aramızda bu kadar mesafe olamaz!
Such heavy-handed swordplay...
Ne kadar vahşi bir kılıç kullanımı.
That small knife is stopping all of Zoro's three-sword-style attacks!
Zoro'nun üç-kılıç stili saldırılarını o küçük bıçak ile karşılıyor.
He out-monsters even the monstrous Zoro!
Canavar Zoro'nun bile ötesinde bir canavarlıkta!
I didn't...
Ben...
I didn't pursue swordsmanship all this time to be a plaything for you and your toy!
Kılıç ustalığını böyle bir oyuncağa heba etmek için öğrenmedim!
You're lucky, Zoro. You were born a boy.
Zoro, çok şanslısın. Sen bir erkeksin.
I want to be the world's greatest swordsman too!
Ben de dünyanın en iyi kılıç ustası olmak istiyorum!
Promise me!
Söz ver bana!
Someday, one of us will be the world's greatest swordsman!
Bir gün, birimiz dünyanın en iyi kılıç ustası olacak!
Promise me!
Söz ver!
– It's a promise!
– Söz!
To become the world's greatest!
Dünyanın en iyisi olmak için!
I'll... get stronger for the both of us now!
Ben... Onun için de güçleneceğim!
I'll get so strong, my name will reach the heavens!
Adım cennete ulaşacak kadar güçlü olacağım!
I'm gonna be the world's greatest swordsman!
Dünyanın en iyi kılıç ustası olacağım!
I promised her...
Ona söz verdim...
I...
Ben...
I did it all to defeat this man...
Her şeyi bu adamı yenmek için yaptım.
What burden do you bear?
Omzundaki yük nedir?
What do you seek in pursuing power, child?
Güç kazandığında ne yapmayı arzuluyorsun, zayıf olan?
Your skill is most impressive. Would you let us join you?
Yeteneğin çok etkileyici. Sana katılabilir miyiz?
We are bounty hunters, fearsome enough to almost make your blood run cold,
Biz ödül avcılarıyız, kanını donduracak kadar korkutucu...
Yosaku and Johnny.
Yosaku ve Johnny'yiz.
Big Bro isn't a child, you cross creep!
Abi'ye zayıf mı dedin? Seni haçlı pislik!
I'll teach you a lesson in manners...!
Sana terbiye dersi vereceğiz!
Stop it, Yosaku and Johnny! Don't get in his way!
Kesin şunu, Yosaku ve Johnny! Ayak bağı olmayın!
Be... patient...!
Sabırlı... olun...!
Luffy...
Luffy...
I... can't afford to lose...!
Ben... kaybedemem...
Tiger...
Kaplan...
I like it!
Harika!
The world's greatest swordsman!
Dünyanın en iyi kılıç ustası!
That's exactly who the Pirate King needs on his crew!
Korsanlar kralının mürettebatında daha azı olamaz zaten!
Trap!
Avı!
Are you just going to let me pierce your heart?
Öylece kalbini deşmeme izin mi vereceksin?
Why aren't you withdrawing?
Neden geri çekilmiyorsun?
I don't know why, but...
Neden bilmiyorum, ama...
if I withdraw even one step,
eğer bir adım bile geri çekilirsem,
it feels as if all the important oaths and promises that I once made will shatter,
geçmişteki sözler ve yeminler gibi önemli birçok şey parçalanacak,
and I won't be able to come back to where I am now.
ve şu anda bulunduğum konuma geri gelemeyeceğim.
Yes. That is defeat.
Evet, yenilgi böyle bir şeydir.
Then, all the more reason I can't withdraw...
O zaman çekilmemem için bir sebep daha.
Even if you'll die?
Ölsen bile mi?
I'd rather die.
Ölmeyi yeğlerim.
What a strong heart!
Ne güçlü bir yürek!
So he chooses death over defeat!
Ölmeyi yenilgiye tercih ediyor!
Kid! State your name.
Çocuk! Adını bahşet.
Roronoa Zoro.
Roronoa Zoro.
I'll remember it.
Bunu hatırlayacağım.
I've not met anyone like you in a while, young man. Thus...
Uzun süre senin gibisini görmedim, güçlü olan. Bu yüzden...
as a swordsman's courtesy, I'll finish you using the world's mightiest black blade.
Bir ustanın nezaketiyle, dünyanın en güçlü kara kılıcıyla işini bitireceğim.
I appreciate it.
Minnettarım.
He took it out!
Sonunda çekti!
He sliced up the ship with that sword!
O, gemiyi doğradığı kılıç!
So this will be the final attack...
Bu son vuruş olacak...
Will I rise to the world's greatest...
Dünyanın en iyisi olmak mı?
or die?
Ölmek mi?
Big Bro! That's enough! Please stop!
Abi! Yeter artık! Lütfen dur!
Three-Sword Style Secret Technique:
Üç Kılıç Stili Gizli Teknik:
Fall!
Yıkıl!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Üç Bin Dünya!
I lost...
Kaybettim...
I never imagined I would lose...
Kaybedeceğimi hiç düşünmemiştim...
So this is the power of the world's greatest...
Demek ki bu dünyanın en iyisinin gücü...
What are you...?
Ne yapıyorsun...?
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame...
Sırttaki yaralar bir kılıç ustasının utancıdır.
Superb!
Harikulade!
Zoro!
Zoro!
Don't rush headlong into the jaws of death, hotshot.
Ölümün kucağına bodoslama atlama, delikanlı.
Zoro!
Zoro!
– Big Bro!
– Abi!
Why?
Neden?
I threw my life away when I decided to be the world's greatest swordsman.
Dünyanın en iyi kılıç ustası olmayı seçtiğimde zaten hayatımı çöpe attım.
He's lost it! His opponent is the actual greatest in the world!
O delirmiş! Rakibi dünyanın en iyisi!
The outcome was obvious!
Sonuç belliydi.
Dying is worse than giving up his ambition!
Ölmek yerine hırsından vazgeçmesi lazımdı!
The choice was easy!
Çok basit lan!
Just abandon your ambition!
Sadece hırsından vazgeç!
So this is the power of the Grand Line... the power of the world!
Demek ki bu Grand Line'nın gücü... dünyanın gücü!
Pirate Hunter Zoro was as helpless as a newborn!
Korsan Avcısı Zoro, yeni doğmuş bir bebek kadar çaresizdi!
Damn you, damn you... damn you!
Lanet olsun, lanet olsun... lanet olsun!
– Big Bro!
– Abi!
Wh-What did he just do?!
O-O da ne?!
So that brat has the power of a devil fruit!
Demek ki o velette şeytan meyvesinin gücü var!
You bast–
Seni–
Are you that young swordsman's comrade?
O genç kılıç ustasının arkadaşı mısın?
You also impressed me for bearing witness till the end.
Sonuna kadar izleyerek beni etkiledin!
Have no fear. Today is not the day he dies.
Merak etme. Onu öldürmedim.
Huh?
Ha?
Big Bro! Big Bro, say something!
Abi! Abi! Bir şey söyle!
Zoro?!
Zoro?!
Zoro!
Zoro!
Hurry, get him on the ship!
Hadi, çabuk olun ve onu gemiye çıkartın!
Pour this medicine on him!
Bu ilacı üzerine dökün!
It's still too early for you to die.
Ölmen için daha çok erken.
My name is Dracule Mihawk!
Benim adım Dracule Mihawk!
Learn about yourself!
Kendini bil!
Learn about the world!
Dünyayı öğren!
And become strong!
Ve güçlen!
No matter how many years it takes,
Kaç yıl geçerse geçsin,
I'll await you with the title of the greatest.
en iyi olarak kalıp seni bekleyeceğim.
Surpass this sword!
Bu kılıcı aş!
Surpass me, Roronoa Zoro!
Beni geç, Roronoa Zoro!
Big Bro! Big Bro, say something!
Abi! Abi, bir şey söyle!
Big Bro!
Abi!
To think that he got Hawk Eye Mihawk to say this much...
Şahin Göz Mihawk’a bunları söyletmiş olması…
Kid, what is your goal?
Çocuk, neyi hedefliyorsun?
King of the Pirates!
Korsanlar Kralı!
That's a feat even more challenging than surpassing me.
Bu beni geçmekten bile zor!
How would I know, when I haven't done it yet?!
Daha olmadan nasıl bilebilirim ki?!
He's alive!
Yaşıyor!
He's just unconscious.
Sadece bayılmış.
Big Bro! Say something!
Abi! Bir şey söyle!
Big Bro!
Abi!
Zoro?
Zoro?
L... Luffy...
L... Luffy...
Can you hear me?
Beni duyabiliyor musun?
Yeah!
Evet!
Did I worry you?
Seni endişelendirdim mi?
You'd struggle...
Ben...
with anything less than the world's greatest swordsman, right?
dünyanın en iyi kılıç ustası olamazsam zorlanırsın, değil mi?
Big Bro! Please don't talk anymore!
Abi! Lütfen daha fazla konuşma!
Big Bro!
Abi!
I...
Ben...
I will never...
Ben bir daha...
be defeated again!
asla yenilmeyeceğim!
Until the day I defeat him and become a master swordsman...
Onu yeneceğim ve gerçek bir usta olacağım o güne dek...
I'll never...
Bir daha asla...
lose again!
kaybetmeyeceğim!
Got any problems with that...
Bununla ilgili bir sorun var mı...
Pirate King?!
Korsanlar Kralı?!
Nope!
Yok!
You're a good team.
İyi bir takımsınız.
I hope we cross paths again.
Sizi bir daha görmek isterim.
Hey, Hawk Eye!
Hey, Şahin Göz!
Didn't you come to take my life,
Benim kellemi almaya gelmedin mi...
the life of Don Krieg, conqueror of the East Blue?
Doğu Mavi'nin hakimi, Don Krieg'in kellesini?
That was my intent, but I've had my fill of fun.
Alacaktım ama yeterince eğlendim.
I'm heading home for some rest.
Dinlenmek için eve geri dönüyorum.
You may have had your fill, but I'm tired of losing to you.
Sana yetmiş olabilir ama ben sürekli yenilmekten bıktım.
D-Don?
D-Don?
Why are you trying to keep him here?
Neden onu burada tutmaya çalışıyorsun?
Here's a parting gift!
Gitmeden önce öl!
It seems he still hasn't learned his lesson...
Tahmin ettiğim gibi... asla dersini almıyor...
Damn! He escaped...
Kahretsin! Kaçtı...
Usopp!
Usopp!
Luffy!
Luffy!
Go! I'll leave Nami to you!
Git! Nami'yi size bırakıyorum!
Got it!
Anladım!
Zoro and I will bring Nami back for sure!
Zoro ve ben, Nami'yi kesinlikle geri getireceğiz!
You just get that cook to join our crew!
Sen de o aşçıyı tayfamıza al!
When all five of us are reunited, let's go...
Beşimiz yeniden bir araya geldiğimizde gidelim...
to the Grand Line!
Grand Line'a!
Yeah!
Evet!
Sounds like a plan!
Bence de güzel plan!
Guys! We ran into some interference, but the real fight starts now!
Beyler! Küçük bir engel ile karşılaştık ama gerçek savaş şimdi başlıyor!
We're taking that ship!
O gemiyi alacağız!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
Boss Man, if I drive them off, can I be done with chores?
İhtiyar, eğer onları uzaklaştırırsam, kamarotluğu bırakabilir miyim?
Be my guest.
Keyfine bak.
"Hawk Eye" Mihawk The Greatest Swordsman in the World
"Şahin Göz" Mihawk Dünyanın En İyi Kılıç Ustası